<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on BSides Amsterdam</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on BSides Amsterdam</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alexandra Charikova</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/alexandra-charikova-e8f118f8-10a2-475f-aa17-9b30b68e632c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/alexandra-charikova-e8f118f8-10a2-475f-aa17-9b30b68e632c/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Passionate about advancing knowledge in application security and challenging industry leaders, Alexandra is a cybersecurity content creator and hosts the podcast &amp;ldquo;The Elephant in AppSec.&amp;rdquo; This podcast brings together cybersecurity professionals and industry leaders to discuss and tackle challenging topics in application security.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arohi Naik</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/arohi-naik-307d5862-f507-4e38-b551-def81d008a0e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/arohi-naik-307d5862-f507-4e38-b551-def81d008a0e/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Arohi Naik is a Security Engineer at SQR and brings both technical depth and a human-focused lens to her work. With a Master’s in Cybersecurity and experience across threat intelligence, incident response, risk management, and GRC she is passionate about creating security solutions that are not just effective, but also inclusive and user-aware.&#xA;A committed advocate for gender equity in tech and a vocal feminist, she works to elevate diverse voices and drive meaningful change in the cybersecurity space. With a lens grounded in empathy and inclusion, Arohi examines how behaviour, psychology, and culture intersect with the security landscape. Whether she’s building threat models or speaking on stage, she brings clarity, and a mission to make security safer, smarter, and more accessible for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob van der Staak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/bob-van-der-staak-7c348910-e086-4ec4-b6e4-be9e54ec35de/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/bob-van-der-staak-7c348910-e086-4ec4-b6e4-be9e54ec35de/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob van der Staak is a Ethical hacker and red teamer at the Dutch Railways. Sharing knowledge is his passion, and with his background in software development and technical informatics, he implements code to assist with his daily assessments.&#xA;From web penetration testing to malware development and cloud technologies, he is eager to learn and share his expertise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fergus Hay</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/fergus-hay-11f5e88c-7184-4368-9b0e-c0e2940b56d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/fergus-hay-11f5e88c-7184-4368-9b0e-c0e2940b56d0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fergus Hay is the Co-Founder and CEO of The Hacking Games, an entertainment, training and talent enterprise committed to creating a generation of Ethical Hackers to make the world safer. With $10.5 Trn forecasted to be lost to Cybercrime in 2025 and 69% of European teenagers having committed a cybercrime/misdemeanor, we are facing a generational crisis. The Hacking Games will inspire, educate and equip this generation to be defenders and not attackers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo van den Toorn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/hugo-van-den-toorn-598f92b5-24e8-45a7-9e59-35883259aaa2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/hugo-van-den-toorn-598f92b5-24e8-45a7-9e59-35883259aaa2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo is former Chief Information Security Officer and has now transitioned back to help other organizations understand adversary tradecraft. With over twelve years of experience in the Information Security industry, he has a solid technical background as hands-on security professional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hugo has experience with and a keen interest in Social engineering, phishing and physical penetration testing. Nowadays, Hugo takes pride and joy in helping individual team members and the business grow. With a strong technical foundation, Hugo combines his passion for security, teaching and hacking with a drive for continuous improvement and optimization of people, processes and technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiggyasu Sharma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/jiggyasu-sharma-afb90e22-1886-4bc7-840a-d1050a7db842/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/jiggyasu-sharma-afb90e22-1886-4bc7-840a-d1050a7db842/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lead Info Sec Engg Consultant at Nike with over 15 years of experience in information and application security, specializing in IOT/OT. My expertise spans web and mobile application security, API/web services, network and wireless security, Bluetooth and Zigbee, embedded device security, and 3G/4G spectrum security, where I have led large-scale security initiatives to strengthen enterprise resilience and enable secure product innovation. I hold OSCP, ECSA, and SANS-561 certifications and am an active member of the global security community, having presented at leading conferences such as RSA, c0c0n, and CysInfo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joey Dreijer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/joey-dreijer-bfdf8ccd-2e44-4def-a337-597e2bffbd18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/joey-dreijer-bfdf8ccd-2e44-4def-a337-597e2bffbd18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Technical Architect at SpecterOps&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kes Greuter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/kes-greuter-3a66f58f-6a1a-42fa-8025-5b600ab9aedd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/kes-greuter-3a66f58f-6a1a-42fa-8025-5b600ab9aedd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korstiaan Stam</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/korstiaan-stam-dae3b7a3-806e-405b-8f26-2e8885f4592e/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/korstiaan-stam-dae3b7a3-806e-405b-8f26-2e8885f4592e/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Korstiaan Stam is the Founder and CEO of Invictus Incident Response &amp;amp; Trainer at DEF CON, BlackHat &amp;amp; BruCON. Korstiaan is a passionate incident responder, preferably in the cloud. Before starting Invictus he was doing IR at PwC and Northwave.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lars Lefebvre</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/lars-lefebvre-9b653c45-134a-4ed2-9ce8-bce4234ed43c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/lars-lefebvre-9b653c45-134a-4ed2-9ce8-bce4234ed43c/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lars is a dedicated Cloud and Application Security Engineer with a strong background in the Cloud Native stack. He’s experienced in managing multi-cloud environments, promoting cloud-native practices, and enhancing security measures in software development lifecycles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leandro Quibem Magnabosco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/leandro-quibem-magnabosco-170193a3-9546-4748-94de-755100396350/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/leandro-quibem-magnabosco-170193a3-9546-4748-94de-755100396350/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lex Crielaars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/lex-crielaars-f5760543-8307-4c9e-b997-47f6cd1132cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/lex-crielaars-f5760543-8307-4c9e-b997-47f6cd1132cc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As the former CTO of one of the largest, dedicated data analytics consultancy companies in the Benelux, Lex has always had an eye for how to transform data into information, knowledge and ultimately: wisdom. He now applies his keen, analytical mind in the detection of anomalies. Things you don&amp;rsquo;t want to see in your security logs but are looking for anyway.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marina Bochenkova</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marina-bochenkova-48615645-061c-4128-90e2-1987ceb235bc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marina-bochenkova-48615645-061c-4128-90e2-1987ceb235bc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marina wears many hats as a cybersecurity analyst focusing on digital forensics, incident response, and OT security, while also dabbling in security awareness and culture. She combines a passion for protecting people, a strong belief in digital privacy as a human right, and an overly-enthusiastic approach to problem-solving. When not defending digital spaces, Marina actively nurtures her already-unhealthy obsession with cats and resorts to baking or martial arts when desperate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markus Einarsson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/markus-einarsson-ae6a0c7a-dcf9-4860-be9a-53e3f46d2a01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/markus-einarsson-ae6a0c7a-dcf9-4860-be9a-53e3f46d2a01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Markus Einarsson is a Security Architect and Incident Response Lead at Sectra in Sweden, where he secures cloud-hosted environments for healthcare customers worldwide. With over a decade of experience in cybersecurity, Markus specializes in incident response, digital forensics and security architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As part of the Sectra Hunt and Incident Response Team, he has extensive hands-on experience with forensic workflows and modern DFIR toolchains. Markus holds multiple GIAC certifications including GEIR, GCDA, GCFE, GCFA, GRID, GNFA, GCIA and GCIH. He is passionate about scalable incident response methodologies and advancing open-source forensic tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marnie Wilking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marnie-wilking-0488ed0b-2ef5-481a-9481-57f736638cfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marnie-wilking-0488ed0b-2ef5-481a-9481-57f736638cfe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marty Wijnen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marty-wijnen-172316b7-845b-4168-b874-1c9d8c7974aa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marty-wijnen-172316b7-845b-4168-b874-1c9d8c7974aa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Ngoma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marvin-ngoma-81456d3b-b74f-4d70-b10f-259f04b1c40a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/marvin-ngoma-81456d3b-b74f-4d70-b10f-259f04b1c40a/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marvin is a seasoned consultant and security architect. He has a strong passion for helping organizations succeed in their cybersecurity programs. He has led many projects in both the private and public sectors, architecting and building Security Operations and Intelligence capabilities; unifying tools, processes, and people. Prior to joining Elastic, Marvin worked as a security consultant at IBM and was the primary SME for QRadar in the nordics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to his work with clients, Marvin frequently speaks at conferences, summits, and meetups on the latest security topics, making him a dedicated security evangelist. He holds a masters in Computer Science &amp;amp; Engineering from Chalmers University of Technology in Sweden, and is a very proactive member of ISC2, among other security bodies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayank Joshi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/mayank-joshi-7666d65d-8020-481c-9629-7c04a06598b6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/mayank-joshi-7666d65d-8020-481c-9629-7c04a06598b6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I try to find and do the hard things before they get harder.&#xA;Believe in building guard-rails and than patching potholes later. Make the secure obvious and the insecure difficult.&#xA;Build trust through a bias towards action and enablement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey De Baets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/mickey-de-baets-3218d458-13fa-44ea-8e9b-cae0284ad723/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/mickey-de-baets-3218d458-13fa-44ea-8e9b-cae0284ad723/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mickey De Baets, a seasoned Penetration Tester, Red Teamer, and currently Lead Offensive Security Engineer at Vectra AI, brings a wealth of expertise in offensive security, focusing on complex threat landscapes. With a strong background in Red Teaming, Mickey actively contributes to cybersecurity education, teaching at Thomas More and hosting community meetups as a Belgian Hack The Box Ambassador&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nohé Hinniger-Foray</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/noh%C3%A9-hinniger-foray-337e0789-6c10-4e16-90d9-88da35a79754/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/noh%C3%A9-hinniger-foray-337e0789-6c10-4e16-90d9-88da35a79754/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nohé is Full-Stack R&amp;amp;D Engineer @ Escape. As computer science enthusiast, he loves to craft new technologies, tools &amp;amp; applications for the open-source community. He has also shared his expertise at various security and tech conferences like BSides Berlin, engaging with a broader audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Moreno</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/paul-moreno-08bb8f29-9c0e-4c96-9a6f-5ce6343e22d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/paul-moreno-08bb8f29-9c0e-4c96-9a6f-5ce6343e22d8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A transformational cybersecurity executive with over 20 years of experience building and leading security teams and programs across diverse industries. I specialize in aligning cybersecurity strategy with business objectives, risk tolerance, and compliance requirements that empower startups and scale-ups to drive growth and innovation while maintaining robust security postures. I&amp;rsquo;ve contributed to multiple successful acquisitions and IPOs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remco van der Meer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/remco-van-der-meer-33c51be0-8aec-4c14-9ad5-02ba4a902b40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/remco-van-der-meer-33c51be0-8aec-4c14-9ad5-02ba4a902b40/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I like Windows security&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhesa Baar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rhesa-baar-8917a5da-312d-43a6-a30f-8b24d08ea169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rhesa-baar-8917a5da-312d-43a6-a30f-8b24d08ea169/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My name is Rhesa, a security enthusiast. I work in the security field for 13 years now. I have a technical background. I have worked as a consultant doing technical threat and vulnerability analysis but also as a security architect at a High Tech company.&#xA;I really enjoy to work on multidisciplinary challenges where people and technology need to be brought together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roald Nefs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/roald-nefs-180bd1d9-532a-4957-9b6e-d373f22d650f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/roald-nefs-180bd1d9-532a-4957-9b6e-d373f22d650f/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a Chief Technolog Officer at Warpnet, Roald uses his acquired skills daily within a variety of context related to cybersecurity. He understands both IT security and IT compliance. Bridging between teams, organizations and people is one of his key skills. He has made several contributions to open source. Roald enjoys tinkering with electronics, hardware hacking and software development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rob van der Veer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rob-van-der-veer-392a8144-9b27-469f-98dd-9ae07eb41866/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rob-van-der-veer-392a8144-9b27-469f-98dd-9ae07eb41866/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rob van der Veer has over 33 years of experience in AI and security, from hacker to CEO.  He open sourced international standardization of AI security by creating the OWASP AI Exchange, as the elected co-editor of the AI Act security standard, contributor to ISO/IEC 27090 and the main author of ISO/IEC 5338 on AI system lifecycle.  As Chief AI Officer at the Software Improvement Group, Rob advises governments, enterprises, and institutions worldwide,  co-founded OpenCRE.org, and has delivered over 300 speaking engagements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rutger Flohil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rutger-flohil-ae8297e1-6ff6-417b-9327-cb626492847b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/rutger-flohil-ae8297e1-6ff6-417b-9327-cb626492847b/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rutger Flohil began his career as a .NET developer, building a solid base in software development before switching gears to focus on cybersecurity. After gaining valuable experience in the Security Operations Center (SOC) of the Dutch TLD, he moved on to his current role as a Red Teamer at Dutch Railways (NS). Rutger enjoys the creative side of security, especially when it comes to writing offensive scripts in Python. Always curious and eager to learn, he’s passionate about discovering new techniques and fresh perspectives to tackle security challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vangelis Stykas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/speakers/vangelis-stykas-a5950a64-a289-47f4-88c6-fd75020fae38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/speakers/vangelis-stykas-a5950a64-a289-47f4-88c6-fd75020fae38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vangelis began as a developer from Greece. Six years ago he realized that only his dog didn’t have an API, so he decided to steer his focus towards security.&#xA;That led him to pursue a PhD in Web Application Security with an extra focus on machine learning. He’s still actively pursuing it.&#xA;He currently applies his skills as a Chief Technology Officer at Atropos, and during his free time, Vangelis is helping start-ups secure themselves on the internet and get a leg up in security terms.&#xA;His love of a simplistic approach to hacking by exploiting vulnerable APIs led him to publish research regarding API controlling ships, smart locks, IP cameras, car alarms, EV chargers, and many other IoT devices. Since our lives are nowadays extremely cyber-dependent, his goal is to convince all companies to never neglect their API security as rush-to-market mentality is almost certain to lead to catastrophic security failure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
